♪ ♪
HEY MAN
WHY AIN'T NOBODY AROUND MAN?
WHATS UP
WHAT THE HELL WHERES ALL
THE PEOPLE AT MAN?
HEY WHATS UP WITH
WHAT IS HE DANCING?
WHAT IS ABT STEP?
DOIN' THE ONE TWOSIE
WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG
WITH Y'ALL? ARE Y'ALL INSANE?
- WHAT YOU MEAN?
- WHATS GOIN' ON?
JUST LISTEN, EVER SINCE
THAT SONG CAME OUT
EVERYDAY THEY'VE
BEEN SHUFFLIN'
MONDAY SHUFFLE,
TUESDAY SHUFFLE
EVERYBODY,
THE WHOLE WORLD!
- I AIN'T SCARED NO SHUFFLIN'
- E-EVERYTHING IT WILL GET IN
YOUR BONES
-THE TWO (MUSIC STARTS TO PLAY)
- SEE WE SMOKIN'
NO NO NO NO
- PUT THESE ON
THEY'RE - HEY MAN,
I AIN'T TIME FOR
YOUR DEMO HOMIE
JUST PUT THEM ON
PUT THESE ON LIKE THIS
♪ PARTY ROCK! ♪
♪ - YOU GOT'EM IN?
- WHAT? VITAMINS? ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ - PLAY ALONG
- HUH? ♪
- CAN'T HEAR, WHAT THE HELL ♪
♪ WHOOOO ♪
♪ PLAY ALONG! ♪
♪ LETS GO! ♪
♪ PARTY ROCK IS IN
THE HOUSE TONIGHT ♪
♪ EVERYBODY JUST
HAVE A GOOD TIME ♪
♪ AND WE GON MAKE
YOU LOSE YO MIND ♪
♪ EVERYBODY JUST
HAVE A GOOD TIME ♪
♪ PARTY ROCK IS IN
THE HOUSE TONIGHT ♪
♪ EVERYBODY JUST
HAVE A GOOD TIME ♪
♪ AND WE GON MAKE
YOU LOSE YO MIND ♪
♪ WE JUST WANNA SEE
YA (SHAKE THAT) ♪
♪ IN THE CLUB PARTY ROCK
LOOKIN FOR YA GIRL? ♪
♪ SHE ON MY JOCK NONSTOP
WHEN WE IN THE SPOT ♪
♪ BOOTY MOVIN WEIGHT LIKE
SHE OWN THE BLOCK ♪
♪ WHERE THE DRANK?
I GOTS TO KNOW, ♪
♪ TIGHT JEANS TATTOO
CUZ I'M ROCK N ROLL ♪
♪ HALF BLACK
HALF WHITE DOMINO ♪
♪ GANG OF
MONEY OPRAH DOE ♪
♪ YO I'M RUNNIN THROUGH
THESE LIKE DRANO ♪
♪ I GOT THAT DEVILISH FLOW
ROCK N' ROLL NO HALO ♪
♪ WE PARTYROCK!! ♪
♪ YEA THAT'S THE CREW
THAT I'M REPPIN ♪
♪ ON A RISE TO THE TOP NO
LED IN OUR ZEPPLIN. HEY! ♪
♪ PARTY ROCK IS IN
THE HOUSE TONIGHT ♪
♪ EVERYBODY JUST
HAVE A GOOD TIME ♪
♪ AND WE GON MAKE
YOU LOSE YO MIND ♪
♪ EVERYBODY JUST HAVE A
GOOD TIME LET'S GO ♪
♪ PARTY ROCK IS IN
THE HOUSE TONIGHT ♪
♪ EVERYBODY JUST
HAVE A GOOD TIME ♪
♪ AND WE GON MAKE
YOU LOSE YO MIND ♪
♪ WE JUST WANNA SEE
YA (SHAKE THAT) ♪
♪ EVERYDAY I'M SHUFFLIN'! ♪
♪ SHUFFLIN' SHUFFLIN' ♪
♪ STEP UP FAST AND
BE THE FIRST GIRL ♪
♪ TO MAKE ME
THROW THIS CASH ♪
♪ WE GETTIN MONEY DON'T BE
MAD NOW STOP, HATIN IS BAD ♪
♪ ONE MO SHOT FOR US
(ANOTHER ROUND) ♪
♪ PLEASE FILL UP MY CUP
(DON'T MESS AROUND) ♪
♪ WE JUST WANNA SEE
(YA SHAKE IT NOW) ♪
♪ NOW YOU HOME WITH
ME (YA NAKED NOW) ♪
♪ GET UP, GET DOWN, PUT YO
HANDS UP TO THE SOUND ♪
♪ PUT YO HANDS
UP TO THE SOUND ♪
♪ GET UP, GET UP,
GET UP, GET UP, ♪
♪ GET UP, PUT YO HANDS
UP TO THE SOUND ♪
♪ TO THE SOUND, PUT YO
HANDS UP, PUT YO HANDS UP ♪
♪ PUT YO HANDS UP,
PUT YO HANDS UP ♪
♪ PARTY ROCK IS IN
THE HOUSE TONIGHT ♪
♪ EVERYBODY JUST
HAVE A GOOD TIME ♪
♪ AND WE GON MAKE
YOU LOSE YO MIND ♪
♪ EVERYBODY JUST HAVE A
GOOD, GOOD, GOOD, TIME ♪
♪ OOH, OH, OH, OH
(PUT YOUR HANDS UP) ♪
♪ OOH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OOH, OH, OH, OH
(PUT YOUR HANDS UP) ♪
♪ (SHAKE THAT) EVERYDAY
I'M SHUFF-FF-LIN' ♪
♪ PUT YO, PUT YO ♪
♪ PUT YO, PUT YO
WHOOOOO ♪
♪ PUT YO, PUT YO ♪
♪ YO HANDS UP ♪
♪ PUT YO HANDS UP ♪
EVERYDAY I'M SHUFFLIN'